<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thirty Days App</string>
    <string name="title_1">The Unseen Compass</string>
    <string name="message_1">"The heart knows the direction, even when the map of the world is blank."</string>
    <string name="title_2">The Echo of Action</string>
    <string name="message_2">"Your legacy is not the silence after you're gone, but the echo of the good work you did while you were here."</string>
    <string name="title_3">Dawn\'s Promise</string>
    <string name="message_3">"Every sunrise is a clean slate, proof that the darkest hour is just a prelude to light."</string>
    <string name="title_4">The Alchemist\'s Secret</string>
    <string name="message_4">"Failure is not the opposite of success; it is the raw material from which success is forged."</string>
    <string name="title_5">The Gentle Power</string>
    <string name="message_5">"Be a mirror to the beauty around you, not a sponge to the negativity that tries to cling."</string>
    <string name="title_6">The River of Time</string>
    <string name="message_6">"Stop trying to dam the past. Let the river of time flow, and build your garden on its fertile banks."</string>
    <string name="title_7">The Quiet Strength</string>
    <string name="message_7">"The loudest wisdom often speaks in a whisper, demanding presence, not attention."</string>
    <string name="title_8">The Art of Enough</string>
    <string name="message_8">"We spend our lives chasing the 'more,' forgetting that the perfect amount is 'enough'."</string>
    <string name="title_9">The Shadow Dancer</string>
    <string name="message_9">"To truly love the light, you must first learn the steps of dancing with your own shadow."</string>
    <string name="title_10">The Builder\'s Hand</string>
    <string name="message_10">"Don\'t wait for permission to create. The best monuments are built by hands that simply began."</string>
    <string name="title_11">The Soul\'s Currency</string>
    <string name="message_11">"Kindness is the only investment that guarantees a return, no matter the market."</string>
    <string name="title_12">The Horizon Line</string>
    <string name="message_12">"The fear of the unknown is simply a lack of imagination about what good could be waiting beyond the horizon."</string>
    <string name="title_13">The Gardener\'s Secret</string>
    <string name="message_13">"You don\'t reap in the season you plant. Patience is the secret fertilizer for every worthy dream."</string>
    <string name="title_14">The Truest Wealth</string>
    <string name="message_14">"The quality of your connections, not the size of your collection, defines your richest life."</string>
    <string name="title_15">The Mountain\'s Lesson</string>
    <string name="message_15">"It\'s not the summit that changes you, but the slow, necessary climb that shows you who you are."</string>
    <string name="title_16">The Quiet Revolution</string>
    <string name="message_16">"Small, consistent acts of discipline are the quiet revolution that rewrites your destiny."</string>
    <string name="title_17">The Broken Path</string>
    <string name="message_17">"A smooth road never makes a skilled driver. Be thankful for the bumps; they are lessons in control."</string>
    <string name="title_18">The Power of Pause</string>
    <string name="message_18">"A moment of stillness can solve a problem that a year of frantic movement could not."</string>
    <string name="title_19">The Inner Fire</string>
    <string name="message_19">"Don\'t let the weather outside dictate the temperature of the fire within your soul."</string>
    <string name="title_20">The Bridge Builder</string>
    <string name="message_20">"Understanding is the bridge. If you only look at differences, you will never see the connection."</string>
    <string name="title_21">The Canvas of Choice</string>
    <string name="message_21">"Your life is a canvas, and regret is just a color you chose not to use. Pick up the vibrant ones today."</string>
    <string name="title_22">The Whisper of Truth</string>
    <string name="message_22">"In an age of endless noise, the search for truth requires a powerful silence."</string>
    <string name="title_23">The Open Hand</string>
    <string name="message_23">"You cannot grasp the new while still clutching the old. True receiving requires an open hand."</string>
    <string name="title_24">The Anchor of Self</string>
    <string name="message_24">"When the world spins fast, anchor yourself in what you know to be unshakably true about who you are."</string>
    <string name="title_25">The Time Traveler</string>
    <string name="message_25">"Stop visiting the past to lament and the future to worry. Be an inhabitant of the only real moment: this one."</string>
    <string name="title_26">The Invisible Barrier</string>
    <string name="message_26">"The only walls that truly trap us are the ones we stop trying to imagine our way over."</string>
    <string name="title_27">The Student\'s Oath</string>
    <string name="message_27">"The wisest person is the one who carries an invisible 'L' on their forehead—for Learner."</string>
    <string name="title_28">The Mosaic of Life</string>
    <string name="message_28">"Your flaws are not mistakes; they are the unique, dark tiles that make your mosaic whole."</string>
    <string name="title_29">The Freedom of Forgiveness</string>
    <string name="message_29">"Forgiveness is unlocking a door and realizing the person who was truly trapped was yourself."</string>
    <string name="title_30">The Power of Small</string>
    <string name="message_30">"A single candle can defy the deepest dark. Never underestimate the power of your small, steady light."</string>
</resources>